Part 2. You will hear a podcast about a large business exhibition which is held every year
in London. First, you have some time to look at questions 11 to 14.
Hello, and welcome to this podcast telling you about our annual business exhibition.
This year, as always, it will be full of the very best speakers, features and innovations.
Let me start by reading some feedback from James Craig, who has exhibited with us for
the past two years. James says, I'm director of a company called TalkCon, which is an office
phone system. The first year we exhibited, we had a stand in the business village where
we made a lot of useful contacts. We also used the breakout area where people could
sit down and relax and try out our products, and due to popular request, we used that
again last year. Last year, we also sponsored the innovative business connection zone, where
people could leave their contact details on a board to contact other companies, and that
also effectively raised our corporate profile. We're hoping that in the coming exhibition,
we'll also have a presence in the digital marketing centre, which is clearly a key area
for our company, and also maybe have our own TalkCon zone at some stage. The exhibitions
open from 8am to 11pm, and there's a range of special events for you to enjoy in the
evening, as well as a unique chance to publicise your company. Businesses who exhibit with
us can claim discounts on a number of popular brands, including major high street fashion
and jewellery outlets, as well as grocery chains. Discounts available range from 3.5%
up to an amazing 15%, so you can save a lot of money. In fact, the average saving made
by each exhibitor came to over £400. The scheme is available to every member of your
organisation, so this is a benefit that really does have something for you all.
Now listen, and answer questions 15 to 20.
Now let me tell you about some of our keynote speakers for this year's exhibition.
Jim Clowery started off selling vegetables from a small plot, then opened a small cafe.
Rather to his surprise, this became a bit of a sensation, and in a remarkably short
time, he had opened an amazing 76 restaurants worldwide. He'll be telling you how it all
happened, and how it changed his life. David France will be giving an inspirational talk
about how, as a business-minded teenager, he managed to set up his own company, and
even to be the first person under 18 to get a business bank account. David's company
has gone from strength to strength, but he isn't just interested in making money. He
also makes regular donations to organisations, helping those in need, both in the UK and
elsewhere in the world. Oliver Stanton was born and educated in the UK, and then went
to Malaysia, where he set up a rubber wood furniture business. He then built log houses
in the mountains in Japan, before moving to Hong Kong to set up a digital marketing business.
After that, he moved back to the UK with his wife Sai Pin, and together they opened a Thai
cafe. He'll be telling you about what he discovered during his travels around the world, about
business practices in different cultures. Francesca Heptonstall is a broadcaster and
businesswoman who is known for her down-to-earth attitude. After winning a top job at a TV
contest, she launched a number of online deal sites. Her main business interest is in technology,
but she's also passionate about helping people gain employment, and organises an annual jobs
fair, so she'll be concentrating on this in her talk. Salman Khan is the chief executive
of QBF Enterprises, and has turned around this business from a major publishing business
to one of the UK's largest digital marketing service providers. He'll be talking about
the need for flexibility to cope with new directions in today's business world.
Finally, Annie Craven is a consultant and coach who works with people to create lasting
changes in their business and life. Her session will offer an interactive look at different
obstacles in people's own lives, not just in business. She also looks at how you can
overcome them, whether you're starting out in business or at the top of your game.
That is the end of part two. You now have 30 seconds to check your answers to part two.